What are you doing awake so early, Goob?
>> I couldn't sleep cuz I'm just so excited
for Dandy's sleepover. So, I'm packing
my lunchbox.
>> Do you need help with that?
>> I want to do it all by myself to show
you I can. Look, I put the dinosaur
chicken nuggies in the big tray. Some
peanut butter and apple slices I cut
myself over here. A couple glass bottles
of my pee for if I get thirsty. And some
crayons so I can draw after lunch. And
you really want to go to this boy's only
sleepover alone?
>> I won't be alone. Roger is going to be
there. And Shrimpo and Finn and Louis
and Astro and Dial and lots of others.
>> Well, you be careful. Boys can be rough
with each other. I don't want them to do
anything that would cause you to become
uncomfortable.
>> Oh, Scraps. I'll be okay. I've got my
dinosaur chicken nuggies.
>> Well, just remember if you need me for
anything or if you want to go home, me
and the girls will be right next door at
Poppy's house having our own sleepover.
>> No, you have fun, too. I don't want to
ruin your night.
>> At least keep my phone number on you the
whole time and and take some of your
fidget toys in case you start stmming.
>> I don't want to bring those.
>> You're not going to be made fun of.
What about your AAC unit? Don't you want
to at least bring that in case you can't
speak properly?
>> No.
>> Sleepovers are more than just bringing
food and games along. Goob, you need to
be prepared.
>> Prepared for what? for your you know you
get overwhelmed and
>> and there it is. You always do this. You
always have to bring it up.
>> Bring what up?
>> That I'm autistic or special or
different. My friends don't see me like
that.
>> They do see it. You can't tell cuz
you're stupid as [__] Your friends see
you as broken and worthless and they
hate you.
>> No. No they don't. I'm normal with them.
I'm just goob.
>> And sometimes goob gets overwhelmed.
Sometimes goop is loud and shuts down or
needs space and is annoying as [__]
>> Why would you say that?
>> Because pretending bad things may never
happen doesn't protect you. It just
means you're unprepared for when it
does. Everyone hates you, including me.
But you have to accept that because I'm
all you got as your caretaker. So listen
up when I'm telling you what to do,
[__] Or I'm calling the government to
come and take you away.
>> I'll prove it to you that today I'm not
autistic.
>> Autism isn't a day-by-day thing, [__]
[__] you're already diagnosed and it's
not going away.
>> Hey, girlfriend. You still coming to my
sleepover?
>> Yeah, I will be down there in 10
minutes.
>> What's wrong, [__] Ah,
you don't sound so confident first thing
in the morning.
>> It's goob. Oh, goop trouble again. Girly
poops. Listen, I get that autistic queer
is like your baby brother and you want
to keep him close to you at all times
for like his safety, but me and the
girls have been talking it over and we
came to the decision that hold on Poppy,
we all said that conversation was had in
secret.
>> Ginger, shut up. Do you want to come to
my sleepover or not? Oh my god,
gingerbread cookie [__] your ass is
flat. Scraps we like are going to stop
being your friend unless you stop
bringing him to all our meetups. We
simply do not appreciate having to be in
the presence of the mentally challenged
when we do not have to be. You
understand?
>> No. No. I get it. You don't have to
worry. Goob is going to his own
sleepover.
>> Oh, that's good. Did you hear that,
girls? Now, if Brighton would just learn
to wipe her ass and not walk around with
a big old poopy butt, we'd have happy
days ahead. Are you worried about him?
Ginger, your voice is annoying us. Stop
it. Thanks for caring, Ginger. But I
know it's for the best. You know, me and
Goop never have alone time. It feels
like me and Goob have never had a day
apart from the moment we were born.
>> Girl, how many times have you sent Goo
down to my bakery to pick up cookies,
and he returned home just fine? He's way
more self-reliant than you're afraid of.
>> You really think so, Cosmo?
>> Hey, I know. So, if a ton can wipe his
butthole just fine after pooping, a
sleepover won't unalive him. And not
counting Brightney, what ton doesn't
know how to wipe their ass?
>> Scraps. You're not going to believe
this. I just sat down on the toilet and
chocolate manifested under me.
>> Goob, no. Don't eat that.
I'm so happy you told me to bring my
fidget toys along. Scraps. I'm going to
give one to everybody.
>> Goo. I really don't care.
>> Everyone gets a different color so all
the tunes knows which is theirs so they
don't get mixed up.
>> Okay. I said I don't give a [__]
>> Can we just act like what happened last
night didn't even happen?
>> I am finding the cowardness of your
feelings in this matter to be rather
unpleasant. Rudy
>> Sylvester, I'm a Christmas tune. You're
a Halloween tune. Just imagine what all
the other tunes in Garden View would
think if they found out you and I. You
know,
>> dust though truly care about what others
think so much.
>> Remember to look both ways for cars.
Goob, wait.
>> Holy [__]
You want to lie, my brother? How could
you monsters?
>> What folly is this? Darting into the
road. Art thou mentally disturbed? This
is no fault of I.
>> Holy [__] I don't want to be a part of
this.
>> Rudy, all shall be well.
>> Sylvester, I just spent a month's worth
of rent to share a bed with a man. We're
well past me being well here.
>> My love, listen to me.
>> Holy [__] It was one night. You are not
about to start calling me love. What do
you think of my new socks, Sprout?
They're kind of gayl looking to be
honest.
>> Hey everybody, look. Sylvester Glisten
and Rudy are here. Now the party can
really start. I'm here too.
>> Sir Gliston brought tamales that he
purchased at the gas station because
they were on discount.
>> Hell yeah. Mexico represent. Sprout will
show you where the food table is.
>> Is anybody going to ask me what happened
to my leg?
>> No thanks, Goob. Glisten before you go.
Do you want to see me dance in my new
socks?
>> Ahaha, yeah. Woo! You go, Dandy.
>> Goob, can you stop? I wasn't showing
you. I was showing Glisten.
>> Sorry, guys. Dandy is really excited
about his new socks, so he wants to show
everybody.
>> I like them cuz they're a rainbow like
me. Goob, I'm going now. Are you sure
you'll be okay?
>> Don't worry about me. You have fun at
your sleepover, too.
>> Hey, [__] Pull up a chair and grab a
Mountain Dew from the cooler. We're
playing the kind of goldfish where we're
betting things like money and [__]
>> Goob, what happened to your leg?
>> I thought nobody would ask. Sylvester
ran me over and the doctor said I will
probably never walk again, but it was an
accident so it's fine. I'm over here so
I don't get in anyone's way.
>> A damn shame. Dandy says he's got a game
plan now that everyone is here. Would
you like to play with us?
>> A game? Oh, this is the most fun day
ever. Everyone grab a piece of paper and
a crayon and write down your name. What
game are we playing? You'll find out
what it is after you write your name.
Cuz I don't want to hear no poopy baby
[__] backing out. Are you backing
out, Shrimpo?
>> [__] I'll take on anything up in
this [__]
>> Okay, we need a hat to draw the names
out of.
>> Astro, you're bald. Give me my hat back.
No.
Shame on you tunes. Laughing at Astro
just cuz he's ugly as [__]
>> Damn forearms and bald. God was not kind
when creating you.
>> Dandy, I've always looked like this.
>> We just never noticed because you're
wearing a sleeping cap all the time.
>> We're tunes. None of us have hair.
>> Sprout does.
>> Those are leaves.
>> Tisha does.
>> That is a literal tissue coming out of
her head. She's a tissue box.
>> Okay, then. Um, Sylvester and his sister
Connie.
>> Okay, fine. The ghost tunes who used to
be human have hair, but literally nobody
else has hair.
>> Oh, Astro, wait. Finn, bring your fat
cheeks over here.
>> Okay, too late to back out now.
>> What are we playing?
>> 7 minutes in heaven. Two of you unlucky
suckers aren't going home till you have
some other tuned saliva in your mouth. 7
minutes in what?
>> 7 minutes in heaven. Closet rules and no
being a poopy baby [__] about who you
get paired up with. Ain't nobody wants
to hear that [__] Who wants first draw?
>> The first name drawn is Sir Goob.
>> Oh, that's me. Goob.
>> Isn't he too autistic for this kind of
game? He's so mentally challenged. I
don't know if he can even consent
properly.
>> Oh, well [__] Would you would you look
at that? It seems me and Goob are making
out tonight. THIS SUCKS. I I HATE GOO.
>> Give me that. This doesn't have your
name on it.
>> Yes, it does. Don't embarrass me.
>> It clearly says Roger.
>> I hate you.
>> Pardon? There must be some mistake. I
didn't even put my name in.
>> I put both our names in. I thought it
was weird that you didn't when you said
we were going to play a game.
>> I see.
>> Rules are rules. Roger, get your fat
cheeks in there.
>> What's wrong, Roger? You're sweating.
>> I am not sweating.
>> We haven't done anything yet.
>> So, you expect us to do something? This
is highly inappropriate.
>> We don't have to. We can just pretend
like we did.
>> They expect us to. And the night just
started. If we come out and say nothing
happened, they'll just laugh at me. Me?
A 67year-old man too afraid to kiss you?
A sexy 19-year-old twink. It makes me
look pathetic.
>> Then let's do it. It's only a kiss. 19
and 67 isn't that big of an age
difference anyway. It only means there's
like 47 years in between us.
If we were to kiss hypothetically, I
would insist it be extremely brief
because even though it's just a game, it
is still illegal for two boys to kiss.
Garden View still enacts the death
penalty on gay tunes.
>> Whatever you want.
>> Hey, what do you guys say we run down to
the McDonald's down the street? Haha,
Sprout, you were so mean drawing Roger
and Goob's name on purpose so that we
don't have to deal with the two tunes
furthest on the autism spectrum for 7
minutes. Cosmo, shut up. They'll hear
you. We all got to make them think we
like them since they're both easy to
push around and it's easy to make them
do things like unclog my toilet and
[__]
>> Let's just pretend like we did it, like
you suggested.
You kissed me. You look like you needed
it.
>> So, what did you guys do? You got to
tell us everything. Those are the rules.
>> Nothing happened.
>> What Roger says?
>> THIS GAME SUCKS.
>> I TOLD you it was a stupid game. We're
going to the kitchen to start making the
Clares. Sprout, you're hurting me. Shut
up.
>> Did you just slap me? I don't appreciate
how confident you've been acting lately.
Oh. Oh,
>> Cosmo, where's the thick white stuff for
the aclarair's? Why are you calling
custard the thick white stuff? You know
what custard is? I thought you were
bringing it. Oh, don't give me that
look. I told you I was bringing the
flour, sugar, and butter. Don't talk to
me. I'm trying to wash the pans.
What? Oh, no. You are not using the
cream on my head. THIS IS MY HAIR.
DONUT. DONUT. DONUT.
>> These are a Claire's goob, not donuts.
>> I don't know what that is, but it sounds
yummy. I want one. Roger. You know
there's no point in feeding that thing
since he's away from scraps. His autism
will lead him to dying in some freak
accident relatively soon.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. It's okay.
>> No, it's not. Leave us alone, Goob.
>> Girls, Roger just texted me something
about what's up, my Sigma Rizzlers.
Guess who's coming with the Eclar's?
>> No, he did not just text you that.
>> He did. And he put three fire emojis.
>> Oh. Oh dear. It's giving pretty
aggressively, too.
>> Now he's asking me if we can grade him
on his aura.
>> That's just not good. Why is he talking
about Aura? The man walks around without
pants.
>> He called me little bro earlier and
tried to dab me up but missed. You're
literally taller than him.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
>> Dandy, why did you even invite Roger to
the sleepover?
>> I didn't. He just showed up and walked
inside while I was holding the door open
for Finn and Shrimpo.
>> You absolutely still could have still
turned him away. We would have turned
the lights off even.
>> He was knocking for 10 minutes. He
wouldn't have just left.
>> Sprout, maybe I should just go home.
>> Roger. Baby girl.
>> They've been talking like that ever
since I got here. I'm so embarrassed.
>> Hey, what are you saying? These aclares
are going to shut them up real quick.
>> Sprout. The cream tastes like piss. I
thought you were better at baking than
this.
>> Don't look at me. Roger made them.
>> What? No, I didn't. Sprout, why are you
lying to them? Sprout is lying. He and
Cosmo made them. I'm just helping by
bringing them out. Sprout, why? Why
would you do this to me?
>> Damn. Can't even make a Claire's
properly and you call yourself a B.
>> Roger, can't you do anything right?
>> All this dancing in my new socks is
making me sweat. Now they're all damp
and smelly.
Do you want me to go handwash them in
the sink?
>> You do that, Astro. For me, you're a
real pal.
Oh, Dandy's rank socks.
They stink so good.
There all washed and squeaky clean.
>> Wow, they're not even wet or anything.
Thanks, Astro. Can you wash them again
if they end up all wet and stinky? I'm
sure they will again before the end of
the night.
>> Whenever you want. I'll just have to
make room in my stink box. That's what I
call my washing machine. You know, stink
box because it makes clothes less
stinky.
>> I'm hungry. You [__] want to get
McDonald's? Yeah.
>> Yeah, a little bit.
>> ABC. If you're going on the McDonald's
run.
>> ABC ABC.
I think somebody is doing a Burger King
run.
>> ABC for Burger King run. ABC for Burger
King. Sorry, Boxton. No starters.
>> Okay, it's our turn to order. What does
everyone want? A Whopper. If you wanted
a Whopper, you should have gone on the
Burger King run. They don't got that
here. What's the closest thing
McDonald's got to a Whopper? How should
I know? I don't eat that Burger King
[__] Is that Gordy Holloway?
Oh, it is. Hi, Gordy.
>> Gordy. Gordy Holloway. We are over here.
He's waving at me. Everybody, stay calm.
You shouldn't be walking around the
McDonald's parking lot all alone, Gordy.
You could get shot.
>> You dare not speak to him. His full
attention belongs to me. Gordy,
greetings. Hello. Good day. I uh
observed your presence from a respectful
distance and was ever so curious about
how your day has been. Have you been
doing anything fun lately?
>> I got a strange text from my mom and dad
asking me to come meet me here, which is
weird cuz I haven't seen them in years.
So, I thought they were, you know, dad
or some [__]
>> Haha, that is so funny. And you are so
sexy and handsome. You know, it was
actually me who sent those texts. I
impersonated your parents to make sure
you'd come.
>> Oh, why?
>> I just wanted to see you silly.
>> Oh, that's really weird. Well, I'm sad
now cuz I was hoping my mom and dad were
really coming home.
>> Sprout, this is weird.
>> Wait, don't walk away. Would you like to
have dinner with us? Mr. Seedley is
here. You like Mr. Seedley, right?
>> Hey, Sylvester, don't make me a part of
this.
>> Well, I think it would depend on what
exactly we'd be having and if you'd be
paying.
>> Dandy, Gordy must be given a Happy Meal
at once. Take my credit card and buy as
many are available.
>> Sylvester, I am not buying Gordy a Happy
Meal.
>> And why will you not?
>> Because we are five grown men and he is
a literal baby on the side of the road.
If we bought him a happy meal, this
whole thing would look weird to the cars
behind us.
>> I wouldn't be on the side of the road if
you let me in the car.
>> Yes. Yes, that is a splendid idea.
Dandy, he speaks true. Unlock the door
so that the pumpkin may hop in and enjoy
the ride of his life.
>> Dandy, I want to go to Burger King.
>> Gordy, stop trying to get free chicken
nuggets. We don't even have room.
>> Sure there is. I'm sure Sylvester would
be just fine letting me sit IN HIS LAP
WHILE I eat as many chicken nuggets he
can buy me with all the money in his
bank account.
>> By the gods above, what crimes have I
dust thou committed to have you send
such a temptress my way and lure me off
my path?
>> Dandicus.
>> Yeah, we're driving across the street to
Burger King. I'm not about to deal with
some [__]
>> Everyone come quick. Roger is up on
Poppy's roof. I think he's going to jump
or something.
>> Oh my god. Is he going to jump? But he's
too sexy to unal alive himself.
>> Roger, come down from there before you
get hurt. Yeah, Roger.
>> Roger. Roger, don't do this. There are
hotlines you can call. Actually, they
always put you on hold for like 3 or 4
minutes, so you might be better just not
calling. So, I don't know. Just come
down.
>> I always knew this [__] was going to
have a mental break. Leave it to Roger
to try and take all the attention away
from me at my own sleepover.
>> What the hell, Roger? Why did you choose
my house to do this on?
>> I don't know why I do a lot of things.
>> Yeah, well, I'm going to have to clean
it up.
Goob, what did you do? Goob, don't
embarrass us.
>> Don't jump, Roger. You are loved.
>> Astro, shut up.
>> Do a back flip.
>> Jump, you coward. Nobody even believed
me when I said I didn't make the eclairs
that were served. I dislike every single
one of you a whole lot right now.
>> Roger.
>> Goob, stay away. Don't try to save me.
>> What are you doing?
>> I'm going to jump cuz I'm depressed as
[__] Is it not obvious? You saw how all
the tunes treated me during the
sleepover. They thought it would be
funny to lock me in a closet for 7
minutes just to see me get flustered
over kissing a breathable white twink
like you. I'm embarrassed just to even
do anything cuz I know I'll be judged.
No one gets what I'm going through.
>> I do. I was thrown in that closet also.
You know they treat me like an outsider.
Isn't that why you walked up to me right
when I got here? Cuz nobody else would
pay attention to me. Let me be here for
you now.
>> Goob, you're too nice for Garden View.
The tunes down there don't deserve to
have you as a friend.
>> But one tune up here does. Come over
here. My sister always tells me that
because I'm autistic, I mess everything
up and I do things wrong. I want to do
at least one thing right tonight.
Please, Roger.
>> Goob. I I just can't.
I'm sorry.
>> Don't apologize.
>> I'm so sorry.
>> I said don't apologize.
>> Thank you for saving me.
>> What?
>> Oh, nothing.
>> It's time to go home, Goob. And by home,
I mean heaven. Because I'm going to unal
alive you and send you back to God.
>> Scraps. What do you mean?
>> You crazy [__]
>> Ha. I'm crazy. You climbed up on the
roof to unal alive yourself in front of
the whole town. And you're calling me
crazy. I'm just going to do what I
should have done a long time ago, and
that is rid myself of my stupid little
brother. I'm done taking care of your
autistic ass goop. I'm sick and tired of
being embarrassed to take you out in
public. What kind of god is up there in
heaven to curse me with a brother who is
autistic, ugly, and gay? You're like the
triple whammy of what it means to be
unlikable, and it pisses me off.
>> If you tried anything against him now,
everyone will see, and you will go to
jail.
>> Um, no. I'm standing over here on the
other side of the roof, away from
everyone's view. All I got to do is
throw this brick from over there, hit
him in his big head, which will be easy
as hell, and knock him off the roof, and
then I will just tell everybody that you
pushed him, Roger. They'll just think
you didn't want to die alone cuz you're
both gay or some [__] Because who would
believe that Scraps, the sweet little
craft tune, is capable of unaliving her
adorable baby brother.
>> Don't move.
>> It's okay. Roger's ass is so big his
butt cheek should cushion his fall.
Why'd you write your name as boob?
>> Goob just looks a lot like boob if you
think about it.
>> If you want cake for dessert, you're not
going to say [__] about what happened on
the roof.
>> I won't. I don't want you going to jail.
You're all I have.
>> The only reason you're still alive is so
we can earn sympathy points from the
other tunes in town. By lying and
telling the other tunes that you and
Roger were best buds, we can try and ask
for twice as many cans of baked beans at
the food bank using your fake sadness.
>> But I really am sad. My heart hurts.
>> It looks like everyone is here because
everyone, specifically those at Dandy's
sleepover last night have led Roger to
successfully unalivvening himself. Dandy
is making me give you all a short
therapy session so that we don't have a
repeat situation cuz it would suck bulls
if this became a common thing.
>> Why is there an open seat?
>> Poppy didn't want to come. She was so
excited that her house was on the front
page newspaper next to Roger's dead body
that she's going down to the photo store
so she can laminate it and hang the
picture on her wall. Typical heartless
[__] but we all know that's Poppy. Got
to respect it. Cosmo came up to me
earlier and requested that because of
Roger's untimely passing, he would like
to perform the half-time performance for
the therapy session this evening, a
commemorative dance in his honor. Cosmo,
you may begin when you're ready.
>> Hit it, girls. R O Dut
E
Roger, I can only hope that wherever you
are in hell, you are able to look up and
watch Cosmo throw it back for you. We
always knew you were a fan of a big fat
dump truck of an ass. And God knows
Cosmo has got the fattest butt cheeks in
all of Garden View.
>> Roger, you may come out now.
>> Roger, you're alive. Look at my new
socks.
Yes, it is true. I am alive.
>> Fortunately, because he is an actual
magnifying glass, he therefore has no
soul. He tells us that when he appeared
before God, God himself asked him where
the hell he came from. And then God sent
him back down here. With a little
Elmer's glue and gay colored band-aids,
we were able to put him back together.
>> Can we go home then?
>> No. For the emotional pain you all
caused, Roger is all still there. and
will likely remain indefinitely.
>> Roger, are we going to tell them about
my sister?
>> What? No, Goob. This moment is about me
right now. I've never been the center of
attention. I'm feeling badass and
valuable.
>> But then it would be a secret. And a
secret is lying. And lying is bad.
>> Goob, someday you will learn honest
people never win. Just look at the
Epstein files. Has a single name in the
Epstein files been held accountable? No.
Because this system protects them. It's
why tunes like you and me are the ones
who suffer. You got to lie in this
corrupt [__] of a world if you want to
survive. You see Sprout standing over
there by the donuts. Watch this.
Give me the donut.
>> What? No, it's mine. Wa yay. Man, you
can't turn him down. He's a survivor.
There's no telling if he'll try doing
something crazy tomorrow. Take the
donut. Roger.
>> You're giving me half.
>> We don't have to share if you don't want
to. It's just uh you said you wanted a
donut last night. So, I take it you like
donuts.
>> You know, I don't feel safe going home
tonight after my sister just tried to
unalive me. Maybe I could stay with you
for a little while.
>> Perhaps we could find an arrangement.
She said, "I don't know what to do."
What?
I said all that I want is you.
I love her so I love her so why.
Oh,
it's so bad.
So
why?
Oh,
it's so bad.
So bad.
She turned to look me the other way.
I didn't know what to do or say
cuz I never love myself.
If only I wish she could see my smile.
See my smile.
If only we could stay a while.
Cuz I love her so I love her so why. Oh
why it's so bad.
So
why?
Oh
so
heat.
Oh, hey [__] I didn't see you there.
I'm Yada from the hit Roblox game
Dandy's World. I'm on my way to work at
my restaurant's Yato's Tacos. How did
you like today's episode? Did you think
it was bitching? That's cool. I thought
it was [__] cuz I was only in it for
like a minute. Hey, if you thought it
was cool as [__] though, you should
support Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 by joining his
Patreon. You can find deleted scenes and
a bunch of gifts that were used in this
episode and all the previous ones. And
also tell him which tunes you want to
see videos centered around next. That's
it. Mama Yata need to go to work at
Yato's Tacos.